<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tefo</string>

    <string name="mojito">Traditionally, a mojito is a cocktail that consists of five ingredients: 
        white rum, sugar (traditionally sugar cane juice), lime juice, soda water, and mint. 
        Its combination of sweetness, citrus, and mint flavors is intended to complement the rum, 
        and has made the mojito a popular summer drink.</string>

    <string name="biryani">Biryani, also known as biriyani, biriani, birani or briyani, is a mixed
        rice dish with its origins among the Muslims of the Indian subcontinent. It is popular throughout
        the Indian subcontinent as well as among the diaspora from the region.</string>

    <string name="poha">Flattened rice, commonly known as chura, is rice which is flattened into flat,
        light, dry flakes originating from the Indian subcontinent. These flakes of rice swell when added to liquid,
        whether hot or cold, as they absorb water, milk or any other liquids.</string>

    <string name="frappe">Frappe is a kind of coffee that is made when you stir instant coffee(in granules)
        together with a small amount of water in a shaker.Add cold water, ice cubes sugar and milk for a proper
        "greek island" experience.Because stirring produces foam, make sure you use a tall glass and a straw</string>

    <string name="dosa">Dosa is a type of pancake originating from the Indian subcontinent, made from a fermented batter. 
        It is somewhat similar to a crepe in appearance. Its main ingredients are rice and black gram. Dosa is a typical 
        part of the Southern Indian and Sri Lankan diets but is now popular all over the Indian subcontinent.</string>

    <string name="burger">A hamburger, beefburger or burger is a sandwich consisting of one or more cooked patties of
        ground meat, usually beef, placed inside a sliced bread roll or bun. The patty may be pan fried, grilled, or
        flame broiled.</string>

    <string name="omlette">In cuisine, an omelette or omelet is a dish made from beaten eggs fried with butter or oil
        in a frying pan. It is quite common for the omelette to be folded around a filling such as cheese, chives,
        vegetables, mushrooms, meat, or some combination of the above.</string>

    <string name="sandwich">A sandwich is a food typically consisting of vegetables, sliced cheese or meat,
        placed on or between slices of bread, or more generally any dish wherein two or more pieces of bread serve
        as a container or wrapper for another food type.</string>

    <string name="pizza">Pizza is a savory dish of Italian origin, consisting of a usually round, flattened base
        of leavened wheat-based dough topped with tomatoes, cheese, and various other ingredients baked at a high
        temperature, traditionally in a wood-fired oven.</string>

    <string name="choco">A petit gâteau, or chocolate fondant, is a dessert composed of a small chocolate cake with
        crunchy rind and mellow filling that is conventionally served hot with vanilla ice cream on a plate. In French,
        the terms for the chocolate cake are "gâteau fondant au chocolat" or simply "fondant au chocolat".</string>


</resources>
